Finding Aid for the Edward C. Weber Papers, 1949-2005
Edward C. Weber Papers
- Correspondence
  - Lomax Poll and Tribune (Los Angeles) (Box 27)
  - Lombardi-Nash, Michael (Box 27)
  - London School of Economics (reference: Science of Revolutionary Warfare by Johann Most) (Box 27)
  - London Workers Bulletin (London) (rejection letter) (Box 27)
  - Long Beach Free Press (Long Beach, CA) (Box 27)
  - Lookout (Seattle, WA) (Box 27)
  - Loomis, Mildred J. (re: donation) (Box 27)
  - Loomis, Ralph (Box 27)
  - Los Angeles Committee for Protection of Foreign Born (Box 27)
  - Los Angeles Free Press (Box 27)
  - Los Angeles Gay Scientists (includes ECW letter explaining Labadie LGBT holdings) (Box 27)
  - Lotta Operaia (Rome, Italy) (Box 27)
  - Lougee, Wendy (from ECW re: purchases and transfers) (Box 27)
  - Loughery, John (reference: history of gay life in U.S. from the 1920s; includes ECW) (Box 27)
  - Louisiana State Library (re: Llano Colonist on microfilm) (Box 27)
  - Louisiana State University (reference: Covington Hall) (Box 27)
  - Louisiana Worker (New Orleans) (Kathryn Davies) (Box 27)
  - Lowe, Malcolm (Box 27)
  - Lowman, Jacquelyn (reference: pacifism and conscientious objection) (Box 27)
  - Lubitz, Wolfgang (reference: American Trotskyist history) (Box 27)
  - Lubkeman, Lynn (reference: Emma Goldman; Agnes Smedley) (Box 27)
  - Lubow, Sylvia (reference: “Digest of California Criminal Syndicalism Cases”) (Box 27)
  - Lumberjack News (Davenport, CA) (Box 27)
  - Lumer, Hyman (re: literary executor of Elizabeth Gurley Flynn) (Box 27)
  - Luna, Nitza (reference: early history of photography in Cuba, Dominican Republic and Puerto Rico) (Box 27)
  - Lunt, Richard D. (reference: UMW and Hitchman Coal case, 1907-1917) (Box 27)
  - Lutte Communiste (Paris, France) (Box 27)
  - Lutte Ouvriere (Belgium) (Box 27)
  - Lutte Ouvriere (Paris, France) (Box 27)
  - Lynch, Enrique (re: possible donation of Marta Lynch Papers) (Box 27)
  - Lynch, Patrick (reference: Jacob Margolis) (Box 27)
  - Lyons, Christopher (re: purchase of Berkeley Independent Socialist Club materials) (Box 27)
  - Lyttle, Bradford (reference: anarchism) (Box 27)
  - Lysander Spooner Society (Box 27)
  - Mabee, Carleton (reference: Sit-ins; civil rights movement) (Box 27)
  - MacGill, Hugh C. (reference: Modern Times, Josiah Warren) (Box 27)
  - MacKay-Gessellschaft, Das Sekretariat der (Hanover, Germany) (Box 27)
  - MacKay Society (New York) (Box 27)
  - Maddaloni, Arnold (Box 27)
  - Mager, Mary Caroline (reference: role of popular culture in the Spanish Republic, 1931-39) (Box 27)
  - Maglin, Arthur (re: subscription information for Crazie Agit-Prop) (Box 27)
  - Magnavite, Laura (reference: candidates for inclusion in Historical Encyclopedia of Chicago Women) (Box 27)
  - Magner, Lois N. (reference: picnic for radicals at home of Eliza Burt Gamble, 1912, etc.) (Box 27)
  - Mahaffy, Cheryl (reference: press coverage of Ford Motor Co., including left press) (Box 28)
  - Mahoney, Ronald J. (reference: The Credit Foncier of Sinaloa by Albert Kimsey Owen) (Box 28)
  - Mainely Gay (Box 28)
  - Maitland, David (Box 28)
  - Makuch, Andrew (Box 28)
  - Malcolm X (Box 28)
  - Malcriado, El (Keene, California) (Box 28)
  - Malet, Michael (reference: Makhnovist and anarchist movements; no reply) (Box 28)
  - Mancini, Matthew (reference: American anarchism 1880-1910) (Box 28)
  - Mandler, Jeffery (reference: British anarchism 1880s to early 1900s) (Box 28)
  - Manikoff, Jane Holt (re: Ford Peace Expedition and Holt Papers) (Box 28)
  - Marcha (Montevideo, Uruguay) (Box 28)
  - Marcus, Irwin M. (reference: Ben Fletcher, IWW) (Box 28)
  - Margaret Sanger Papers (reference: Patrick Quinlan, John Rompapas, John Nicholas Beffel) (Box 28)
  - Margolies, Rick (reference: Agnes Inglis’s manuscript on cooperatives) (Box 28)
  - Marijuana Review (Mill Valley, CA) (Box 28)
  - Mark, Arthur (reference: Ferrer Modern Schools in the U.S.) (Box 28)
  - Marquette University (re: Dorothy Day Catholic Worker Collection) (Box 28)
  - Marsh, Margaret S. (Box 28)
  - Marsiske, Hans-Arthur (Wilhelm Weitling) (Box 28)
  - Martel, Frank X. (reference: Voltairine de Cleyre; literary heir) – file not in box (Box 28)
  - Martel, Frank X. (re: 1952 donation from Detroit and Wayne County Federation of Labor) (Box 28)
  - Martin, James J. (Box 28)
  - Martin Luther King, Jr. Memorial Center and Papers Project (Box 28)
  - Martin Sostre Defense Committee (Box 28)
  - Martin, Virginia (reference: Joe Hill, IWW) (Box 28)
  - Martucci, Enzo (Box 28)
  - Marx Memorial Library (Box 28)
  - Marxist-Leninist Party USA – Detroit Branch (Box 28)
  - Maryknoll Fathers (Box 28)
  - Maryland, University of (re: Human Rights Project) (Box 28)
  - Massillon Museum (reference: Jacob Sechler Coxey) (Box 28)
  - Masters, Anthony (reference: Emma Goldman’s literary heir) (Box 28)
  - Matonis, Jon (reference: monetary freedom movements; E.C. Riegel) (Box 28)
  - Matthesius, Joachim (Box 28)
  - Mattachine Midwest (Box 28)
  - Matthews, Henry (reference: Voltairine de Cleyre) (Box 28)
  - Maverick (Santa Clara, CA) (Box 28)
  - Mayday (See Hard Times) (Box 28)
  - Mayer, Henry C. (reference: Journal of the Knights of Labor; coal mine unions) (Box 28)
  - McAdam, Doug (reference: Freedom Summer; Bob Moses (Box 28)
  - McCabe, Terrence W. (reference: IWW; was present at some events in 1918-1922) (Box 28)
  - McCallister, Frank (Box 28)
  - McClelland, John M., Jr. (reference: Ralph Chaplin; IWW; Labadie Collection history during the 1950s) (Box 28)
  - McClure, Betsy (Box 28)
  - McCool, B. B. (reference: IWW; 1919 Chicago raid on Communists-Spartacan movement) (Box 28)
  - McCormack, A. Ross (reference: IWW in the Canadian West) (Box 28)
  - McCormick, Charles H. (reference: Jacob Margolis) (Box 28)
  - McCown, Robert A. (re: Midwest Archives Conference panel, Documenting the Extremes, 1984) (Box 28)
  - McDade, Thomas M. (reference: Mooney-Billings case) (Box 28)
  - McDaniel, George W. (reference: Smith Wildman Brookhart) (Box 28)
  - McElroy, Wendy (re: index to Liberty) (Box 28)
  - McEvoy, James (re: return of 400 xerox copies of letters) (Box 28)
  - McFadden, Charles (reference: Theodore Roosevelt; Charles F. Potter; Arthur Garfield Hays) (Box 28)
  - McGarvey, Bruce E. (re: donation of Karl E. Pauli Papers) (Box 28)
  - McGill-Queen’s University Press (reference: photograph of Mikhail Bakunin) (Box 28)
  - McGregor Magazine Agency (Box 28)
  - McKinley, Blaine (reference: Voltairine de Cleyre; Anarchos Institute; Haymarket (Box 28)
  - McLay, Farquhar (re: publications from Clydeside Press) (Box 28)
  - McLean, Lois C. (reference: Mother Jones) (Box 28)
  - McLellan, D. (re: sending gay publications from U.K.) (Box 28)
  - McLoughlin, Doris (re: Workingmen’s Institute Library at New Harmony) (Box 28)
  - McNabb, Willis J., III (reference: general inquiry about holdings on sexual relations) (Box 28)
  - McNeal, Merritt (re: Humbolt) (Box 28)
  - McWhorter, George T. (re: University of Louisville’s Ishill/Oriole Press holdings, etc.) (Box 28)
  - Measure (New York) (Box 28)
  - Meditation Centre Kosmos (Amsterdam) (Box 28)
  - Meixner, Laura L. (reference: photo from Red Portfolio: Cartoons for Socialism) (Box 28)
  - Meister, George (re: donation of IWW membership book dated 1919) (Box 28)
  - Melancou, Philip (reference: Henry S. Salt) (Box 28)
  - Mellon, Katherine M. (reference: Ethel A. Johnson; The Crusader; Did You Know?) (Box 28)
  - Mellon, Knox, Jr. (reference: Job Harriman) (Box 28)
  - Meltzer, Albert (re: Black Flag; Kate Sharpley Library) (Box 28)
  - Menta, Ed (reference: materials for production of Joe Hill at Kalamazoo College) (Box 28)
  - Mercantile Library (reference: John Francis Bray) (Box 28)
  - MERIP Reports (Middle East Research & Information Project) (Box 28)
  - Merkel-Melis, Renate (reference: Edward Aveling; Circular to the Sections of the Socialist Labor Party) (Box 28)
  - Merriam-Webster Company (re: errors Webster’s Biographical Dictionary) (Box 28)
  - Messer-Kruse, Timothy (reference: photograph of Joshua King Ingalls) (Box 28)
  - Metro, The (Detroit) (Box 28)
  - Metro-Cat of Rochester (Rochester, NY) (letter from ECW) (Box 29)
  - Metro Times, The (Detroit) (Box 29)
  - Mett, Roderick Michael (reference: anarcho-syndicalist social theory during the Spanish Civil War) (Box 29)
  - Metzler, Marshall (reference: Scott Nearing; Gustavus Myers; Matthew Josephson) (Box 29)
  - Mewitt, Alan (re: death of Mewitt; reminiscences from ECW) (Box 29)
  - Meyer, Stephen (reference: UAW in Detroit, 1905-1921) (Box 29)
  - Meyers, Arthur S. (reference: resources for underground press materials in libraries) (Box 29)
  - Michael, Jason (personal letter from ECW about his relationship with his father, no reply) (Box 29)
  - Michel, Dee (re: Thesaurus for Lesbian and Gay Studies) (Box 29)
  - Michelson, Clare (Box 29)
  - Michigan Alliance of Cooperatives (Box 29)
  - Michigan Archivists Association (re: bibliography of manuscript collections in Michigan libraries) (Box 29)
  - Michigan Dept. of State (Box 29)
  - Michigan Historical Collections (see also: Bentley Historical Collection) (Box 29)
  - Michigan Historical Museum (reference: photos for exhibit on Michigan history) (Box 29)
  - Michigan Militant Newsletter (Detroit) (Box 29)
  - Michigan NORML (Box 29)
  - Michigan Organization for Human Rights (MOHR) (Box 29)
  - Michigan Review (Box 29)
  - Michigan State University (Box 29)
  - Microfilming Corporation of America (Box 29)
  - Midnight Special (New Orleans, LA) (Box 29)
  - Midwest Libertarian Library Association (Box 29)
  - Mihelic, Mrs. Thelma (re: donation of issues of Labor Herald) (Box 29)
  - Mile High Underground (Denver, CO) (Box 29)
  - Miles, Barry (reference: biography of William S. Burroughs) (Box 29)
  - Miles, Dione (Box 29)
  - Miles, Robert E. (Box 29)
  - Militant, The (New York) (Box 29)
  - Millar, F. David (reference: Canadian ALU, WFM, IWW, SLP, SLTA) (Box 29)
  - Miller, Ed (Box 29)
  - Miller, Howard S. (reference: Kate Austin, includes letter from her literary heir) (Box 29)
  - Miller, Jay (reference: Thybald Trust’s Wild Irons) (Box 29)
  - Miller, Joseph T. (reference: Josiah Warren) (Box 29)
  - Miller, J. Wesley (re: 1960s radicalism; article on Madison poster collection) (Box 29)
  - Miller, Martin A. (reference: Kropotkin, T. Piro) (Box 29)
  - Miller, Mitchell H. (from Libertarian Workers Group) (Box 29)
  - Miller, Robert J. (reference: photograph of Hastings William Sackville Russell Bedford) (Box 29)
  - Miller, Sally M. (reference: Johann Most; Emma Goldman; Alexander Berkman; Knights of Labor) (Box 29)
  - Miller, Timothy (re: 60s Commune Project donation from University of Kansas) (Box 29)
  - Miller, Worth Robert (reference: Henry Vincent) (Box 29)
  - Millet, Martha (re: offer of poetry, literary and social criticism) (Box 29)
  - Mindszenty Report (St. Louis, MO) (Box 29)
  - Miner’s Art Group (Box 29)
  - Mineworker, The (Doncaster, Yorks, England) (Box 29)
  - Minnegasco (re: seeking radical literature on how to steal gas) (Box 29)
  - Minnesota Center for Book Arts (re: loan of lesbian periodicals for exhibition)\ (Box 29)
  - Minnesota Coalition for Battered Women (reference: seeking issues of Out and About) (Box 29)
  - Minnesota, University of (re: donation of anti-communist and right wings pamphlets) (Box 29)
  - Minnesota University Women’s History Sources Survey (Box 29)
  - Minus 5 (Hong Kong) (Box 29)
  - Mirror (Guyana, South America) (Box 29)
  - Mishark, John W. (re: offer of 19th century German radical literature) (Box 29)
  - Missey, Jim (reference: Ammon Hennacy; Christian anarchism; Catholic Workers) (Box 29)
  - Mississippi Free Press (Jackson, MS) (Box 29)
  - Mississippi Gay Alliance (Box 29)
  - Mississippi Newsletter (Tougaloo, MS) (Box 29)
  - Missouri Historical Review (reference: Emma Goldman) (Box 29)
  - Mitts, Chuck (Box 29)
  - Mizell, Michael (reference: Mary Marcy; Lucy Parsons (Box 29)
  - Mockingbird Press (includes note from Tuli Kupferberg) (Box 29)
  - Modesto, Zapata (reference: Joe Hill) (Box 29)
  - Mole, The/Old Mole (Cambridge, MA) (Box 29)
  - Mole Express (Manchester, England) (Box 29)
  - Molin, L. (reference: Free Society) (Box 29)
  - Monaghan, Jim (reference: Patrick Trench; Lois Orr (Box 29)
  - Money (Craryville, NY) (Scott, John G., ed.) (re: Inglis; Mother Earth) (Box 29)
  - Monroe Defense Committee (Box 29)
  - Monsen, Anders (reference: European individualist anarchists) (Box 29)
  - Montana: The Magazine of Western History (reference: photographs for article on IWW) (Box 29)
  - Montano, Randolph (reference: Lois Orr literary rights) (Box 29)
  - Montgomery, Jeffery (letter to Anne Oakey) (Box 29)
  - Montrose Voice (Houston, TX) (Box 29)
  - Moody, J. Carroll (reference: steelworks; National Recovery Administration 1929-1935) (Box 29)
  - Mooers, Deborah S. (reference: IWW cartoons and posters) (Box 29)
  - Moore, E. B. (re: donation of photographs of South Dakota during the harvest of 1916) (Box 29)
  - Moore, Joseph (reference: was Augusto Sandino an anarchist?) (Box 29)
  - Moores, Harold S. (reference: American freemasonry) (Box 29)
  - Moral Re-Armament (Box 29)
  - Morea, Benn (re: subscription to Black Mask) (Box 29)
  - Morell, Gilbert W. (reference: letter to Sidney Fine re: Illinois labor movement after WWI) (Box 30)
  - Moreno, M. (re: Partido Obrero de Unificación Marxista) (Box 30)
  - Mornati, Fiorenzo (reference: Vilfredo Pareto) (Box 30)
  - Mornin, Edward (reference: John Henry Mackay) (Box 30)
  - Morris, David (reference: Carl Harp) (Box 30)
  - Morris, George ( The Worker) (Box 30)
  - Morris, James K. (reference: The Can Opener) (Box 30)
  - Morris, John P. (reference: Joseph Buchanan) (Box 30)
  - Morton, Marion J. (reference: Emma Goldman, for his book, Nowhere at Home) (Box 30)
  - Moslem Students Society (Box 30)
  - Mountain Review (Whitesburg, KY) (Box 30)
  - Mother (Stanford, CA) (Box 30)
  - Mother’s Defense Committee (Box 30)
  - Mothershed, S. W. (re: from ECW about clearing house for librarians on Black History—no reply) (Box 30)
  - Motive Magazine (Nashville, TN) (Box 30)
  - Moure, Daniel Seijas (re: translation of L. Labadie essay; offer to sell Spanish books) (Box 30)
  - Mouth of the Dragon Press (New York) (Box 30)
  - Movement, The (San Francisco) (Box 30)
  - Movement for a New Society (Philadelphia) (Box 30)
  - Movement for Colonial Freedom (London) (Box 30)
  - Movimiento Liberatario Cubano (Miami) ( Guángara Libertaria) (Box 30)
  - Movimento Libertário Portugues (Lisbon) (Box 30)
  - Movimento Nonviolento (Verona, Italy) (Box 30)
  - Movimento por la Paz (Cuba) (Box 30)
  - Mugford, Eldred George (re: donation of his dissertation: The Film Producer and His Craft) (Box 30)
  - Muhammad Speaks (Chicago) (Box 30)
  - Mujeres Libres (France) (Box 30)
  - Mullholland, Kate (Catherine) (Box 30)
  - Muller, Robert H. (reference: questions by anti-Semitic and right wing materials are in the Labadie) (Box 30)
  - Munksgaard International Publishers (reference: Joe Hill) (Box 30)
  - Muñoz, V. (reference: American libertarians; The Peaceful Revolutionist; donation of books) (Box 30)
  - Muntaqim, Jalil Abdul (re: request for a copy of his pamphlet for the Labadie) (Box 30)
  - Murphy, J. Austin (re: donation of his book to the Labadie) (Box 30)
  - Murphy, Mary (reference: Women in the IWW (Box 30)
  - Murray Newsletter (Box 30)
  - Murry, Bernice E. (reference: Mother Earth Bulletin; Voltairine de Cleyre; The Word; etc.) (Box 30)
  - Murtagh, Pat (reference: history of anarchism in Canada) (Box 30)
  - Museum of African American History (re: loan of materials for exhibition on Black Newspapers) (Box 30)
  - Museum of North Idaho (re: loan of materials for exhibition on labor history) (Box 30)
  - Museum of Photographic Arts (re: loan of materials for exhibition on Worker Photography (Box 30)
  - Music Sales Corporation ( Sing Out) (Box 30)
  - Musser, Necia (reference: The Crusader Newsletter) (Box 30)
  - Mutch, George E. (3 folders) (Box 30)
  - Mutnick, Barbara (re: donation of pamphlets by Trotsky and Schachtman) (Box 30)
  - Myers, Brian W. (reference: general) (Box 30)
  - Myers, Michael (reference: Lucy Parsons; Cassius Cook; Carl Nold) (Box 30)
  - Myers, William F. (reference: movements against Italian fascism; Tresca; Salvemini; Rolland; etc.) (Box 30)
  - N.S.C.A.R. (National Student Coalition Against Racism: Student Mobilizer) (Box 30)
  - N.U.C. (New University Conference) (Box 30)
  - Nadel, Stanley (reference: Protocols of the Internationale Möbel-Arbeiter) (Box 30)
  - Naftel, Avi (Box 30)
  - Naiko, Grace K. (Box 30)
  - Naison, Mark (reference: Communist Party in Harlem during the Depression) (Box 30)
  - Nash, George H., III (reference: Communism in the U.S. 1930s and 40s) (Box 30)
  - National Alliance (New York) (Box 30)
  - National Archives of Canada (re: Eva Langbord and Emma Goldman) (Box 30)
  - National Chronicle (Hayden Lake, Idaho) (Box 30)
  - National Coalition of Black Gays (Box 30)
  - National Committee Against Discrimination in Housing (Box 30)
  - National Committee for Rural Schools (Box 30)
  - National Council for Civil Liberties (U.K.) (Box 30)
  - National Economic Council, Inc. (Box 30)
  - National Film Board of Canada (reference: Labour movement in Canada, IWW) (Box 30)
  - National Forecast (Topton, NC) (Box 30)
  - National Front News (Croyden, Surrey, England) (Box 30)
  - National Gay Archives (Los Angeles) (Box 30)
  - National Gay Student Center (Washington DC) (Box 30)
  - National Geographic Society (reference: “The Rebel Girl”) (Box 31)
  - National Guardian (New York) (Box 31)
  - National League for Social Understanding (Los Angeles) (Box 31)
  - National Peace Literature Service (Box 31)
  - National Right to Work Committee (Box 31)
  - National Socialist White People’s Party (Arlington, VA) (Box 31)
  - National Task Force on Prostitution ( Coyote Howls) (Box 31)
  - National Urban League (reference: Black nationalist materials) (Box 31)
  - Needham, Claire (Box 31)
  - Negro Universities Press (reference: The Messenger) (Box 31)
  - Neidle, Cecyle (reference: anarchism in the U.S.; Agnes Inglis) (Box 31)
  - Nelson, Garrison (reference: Truman Nelson) (Box 31)
  - Nelson, Truman (reference: Ezra Heywood; Lucifer) (Box 31)
  - Nelson, Walter M. (re: donation of The Liberator; Agnes Inglis) (Box 31)
  - Nemeth, Luc (reference: Michele Schirru) (Box 31)
  - Neperiodajo (Japan) (letter in Esperanto) (Box 31)
  - Nestle, David (re: PopReal) (Box 31)
  - Nettleton, Allan (reference: IWW, Everett) (Box 31)
  - Neufeld, John (reference: Joseph Labadie and his printshop) (Box 31)
  - Neuhaus, John (reference: IWW music and songbooks; Industrial Worker) (Box 31)
  - New Agora, The (Lansing, MI) (Box 31)
  - New Albania (Tirana, Albania) (Box 31)
  - New America (New York) (Box 31)
  - New American Movement (Chicago, IL) (Box 31)
  - New City Songster (Kent, England) (Box 31)
  - New Dawn (San Francisco, CA) (Box 31)
  - New England Free Press (Boston, MA) (Box 31)
  - New Guard: See Young Americans for Freedom (Box 31)
  - New Horizons for Youth (Philadelphia, PA) (Box 31)
  - New Left Notes (Boston, MA) (Box 31)
  - New Life (London, England) (Box 31)
  - New Mexico Review & Legislative Journal (Santa Fe, NM) (Box 31)
  - New Mexico State University Chicano Affairs Office (re: subscription to La Raza Habla) (Box 31)
  - New Order (Arlington, VA) (Box 31)
  - New Patriot (Chicago, IL) (Box 31)
  - New Politics (New York) (Box 31)
  - New Solidarity (New York) (Box 31)
  - New Spectre (Bath, Somerset, England) (Box 31)
  - New Voice (Sacramento, CA) (Box 31)
  - New World Review (New York) (Box 31)
  - New York City League for Sexual Freedom (Box 31)
  - New York Labor News (Box 31)
  - New York Public Library (Box 31)
  - New York School of Printing (reference: Josiah Warren) (Box 31)
  - New York University. Tamiment Library (Box 31)
  - New Yorker Films (re: Improper Conduct-documentary about Cuban homosexuals) (Box 31)
  - Newbill, James (reference: IWW; Yakima Valley 1933) (Box 31)
  - Newborn Rights Society (Box 31)
  - Newman, Edgar Leon (reference: French worker poetry of the 19th century) (Box 31)
  - News From Nowhere (Edmonton, Alberta) (Box 31)
  - Newsman’s Gadfly (Mt. Vernon, IA) (Box 31)
  - Newsstatements (Quebec, Canada) (Box 31)
  - Newswest (Los Angeles, CA) (Box 31)
  - Newton, Robert (Box 31)
  - Ngai, Mae M. (reference: deportation of Chinese-American leftists in the 1950s) (Box 31)
  - Nick, George (1 of 12 folders) (Box 31)
  - Nick, George (2 - 6 of 12 folders) (Box 32)
  - Nick, George (7 - 12 of 12 folders) (Box 33)
  - Nickel Review (Syracuse, NY) (Box 33)
  - 1976 Committee, The (Des Plaines, IL) (Box 33)
  - Nishimoto, Koichi (reference: Daniel De Leon; Socialist Labor Party) (Box 33)
  - Nissen, Tony (reference: organized labor in the U.S. during the Civil War) (Box 33)
  - Nkoli, Simon (letter from ECW-no reply) (Box 33)
  - Nkombo (New Orleans, LA) (Box 33)
  - No Limits (Madison, WI) (Box 33)
  - No More Fun and Games (Cambridge, MA) (Box 33)
  - Noir et Rouge (Paris, France) (Box 33)
  - Nomad, Max (re: donation of his library) (Box 33)
  - Non-Aligned Members of the June 12th Coalition (Box 33)
  - Nonoyama, M. (reference: Leviatán; La Libertad; Solidaridad Obrera; Blanco) (Box 33)
  - Nordland Press ( TRUD!)(Essex Falls, NJ) (Box 33)
  - North bi Northwest (Seattle, WA) (Box 33)
  - North Carolina Center for Student Rights (Box 33)
  - North Carolina Coalition for Gay & Lesbian Equality (ECW gifts justification for collecting LGB) (Box 33)
  - North Carolina University Library (reference: The Crusader; Robert F. Williams) (Box 33)
  - North Country Anvil (Millville, MN) (Box 33)
  - North Star (Berkeley, CA) (Box 33)
  - Northern Ireland Gay Rights Association (Belfast) (includes report of 1976 DUP repression) (Box 33)
  - Northern Micrographics, Inc. (reference: radicalism of the right) (Box 33)
  - North-West Archives and Labour History Project (Derry, Northern Ireland) (Box 33)
  - Northwestern University Library (re: exchange of materials and procedures) (Box 33)
  - Notarstefano, F. (re: offer to donate libertarian materials) (Box 33)
  - Nouvel Ordre Social (Geneva, Switzerland) (Box 33)
  - Novak, Derry (reference: Peter Kropotkin) (Box 33)
  - Nova Falç, La (Perpignan, France) (Box 33)
  - Now! Magazine (San Francisco, CA) (Box 33)
  - Nowlin, Bill (reference: Emma Goldman; Alexander Berkman; includes note from Ian Ballantine) (Box 34)
  - Nuestra Lucha (Immokalee, FL) (Box 34)
  - Nungesser, Lonnie G. (reference: homosexual stereotypes (Box 34)
  - Nuntius, The (Houston, TX) (re: Our Community) (Box 34)
  - Nuovi Tempi (Rome, Italy) (Box 34)
  - O Protesto (Brazil) (Box 34)
  - O.S.P.A.A.A.L. (Havana, Cuba) (Box 34)
  - Oakland Post (Berkeley, CA) (Box 34)
  - Oakland Unified School District (Box 34)
  - Oakland University (reference: underground press publications) (Box 34)
  - Objectivist (New York, NY) (Box 34)
  - O’Brien, Francis L. (re: jury duty for ECW) (Box 34)
  - O’Brien, George Harman (reference: Lillian Harman’s descendants; donations to Labadie Collection) (Box 34)
  - Obvious, The (Weare, NH) (Box 34)
  - O’Bryan, Mike (reference: United Mine Workers Journal) (Box 34)
  - O’Connor, Thomas F. (reference: origin of the Sacco-Vanzetti trial; John Nicholas Beffel) (Box 34)
  - Oestreicher, Richard (reference: photographs for his book, Solidarity and Fragmentation) (Box 34)
  - Of Human Rights (Washington DC) (Box 34)
  - Off Our Backs (Washington DC) (Box 34)
  - O’Gorman, Angie (reference: Gertrude B. Kelly) (Box 34)
  - O’Hair, Madalyn Murray (Box 34)
  - Ohio Lesbian Archives (Box 34)
  - Ohio State University (Box 34)
  - Okike (Amherst, MA) (Box 34)
  - Olmsted, Audrey (reference: Elizabeth Gurley Flynn) (Box 34)